School of the Museum of Fine Arts Records UA133
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Student Affairs records, circa 1876 -- 2016; UA133.005; 469.19 Linear Feet 388 record cartons; 5 card catalog boxes/10 drawers; 5 card boxes
  - January 2017 accession, circa 1876 -- 2010; UA133.005.002; 12.17 Linear Feet
    Microfilmed records from 1876-1962 located in Box 2 (microfilm reels 4996-5002 and 5050) originally microfilmed by and also located in the Archives of American Art. https://www.aaa.si.edu/collections/school-museum-fine-arts-boston-records-6581
    This sub-series contains student records and early SMFA records.
    Student records largely date from 1876 to 1957, and contain information about years of attendance, classes, scholarships, and awards, as well as remarks and notes from faculty members about students. The first set of student records date roughly from 1876 to 1930 and are index cards housed in wooden card catalog drawers, with numbers on each card corresponding to a page number in the registration ledgers housed in the box labeled "Register of pupils." Also in the wooden card catalog drawers are an index to the scrapbooks found on microfilm, and an index to early administration and committee meetings. The second set of student records date roughly from 1930 to 1957 and contain the actual registration card, usually with a photograph attached. The chronological dividing line of 1930 isn't exact; registration methods changed during the period coinciding with the move to the building at 230 The Fenway in 1928.
    Early SMFA records include Annual Reports, course catalogs, and correspondence.
    This sub-series contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list.
    University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
    Records containing information related to student education, staff and faculty employment, and Board of Trustees records are closed for 75 years from the date of creation.
    Some boxes may contain both types of restricted material. This series may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
    - Early SMFA records, reference material, course catalogs, scrapbooks microfilm, 1876 -- 2008; UA133.005.002.002 (Box 2)
      Student records and development records closed 75 years from date of creation. Administrative records closed 20 years from date of creation.
    - Photographs and course registration guides, 1888 -- 2004; UA133.005.002.003 (Box 3)
    - Student records: student registration index A-F, circa 1879 -- 1930; UA133.005.002.013 (Box 13)
    - Student records: student registration index G-P, circa 1879 -- 1930; UA133.005.002.014 (Box 14)
    - Student records: student registration index Ph-Z, circa 1879 -- 1930; UA133.005.002.015 (Box 15)
    - Student records: student registration index Summer school, Evening school, Married name changes, circa 1879 -- 1930; UA133.005.002.016 (Box 16)
    - Index of scrapbooks, circa 1879 -- 1930; UA133.005.002.017 (Box 17)
    - Student records: Register of pupils, circa 1876 -- 1930; UA133.005.002.024 (Box 24)
      - Register of Pupils No. 1 1-492, 1876 -- 1930; UA133.001852; 1 Volumes; 1 Digital Object(s); 450 Megabytes (Box 24)
      - Register of Pupils No. 2 493-1000, 1876 -- 1930; UA133.001853; 1 Volumes; 1 Digital Object(s); 43.6 Megabytes (Box 24)
      - Register of Pupils No. 3 1001-1167, 1876 -- 1930; UA133.001854; 1 Volumes; 1 Digital Object(s); 31.4 Megabytes (Box 24)
    - Student records: student registration cards A-C, circa 1930 -- 1957; UA133.005.002.019 (Box 19)
    - Student records: student registration cards D-H, circa 1930 -- 1957; UA133.005.002.020 (Box 20)
    - Student records: student registration cards I-N, circa 1930 -- 1957; UA133.005.002.021 (Box 21)
    - Student records: student registration cards O-T, circa 1930 -- 1957; UA133.005.002.022 (Box 22)
    - Student records: student registration cards U-Z, Misc, circa 1930 -- 1957; UA133.005.002.023 (Box 23)
  - 2018 accessions, 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.003; 426 Linear Feet 355 Record Cartons
    This sub-series is arranged in alphabetical order. Files within boxes are roughly alphabetical, with some exceptions.
    This sub-series contains student records from circa 1945--2015, which may contain application materials, transcripts, and advising records including information about years of attendance, classes, scholarships, and awards, as well as remarks and notes from faculty members about students and evaluations of their work by the review board. Files often contain photographs of students, and may contain information about students who did not matriculate or graduate from the SMFA. Other formats found in files include slides and printed materials documenting student work.
    Transferred by the SMFA, 2018, accession UA-2018-030.
    These records were maintained in SMFA's Student Services file room in the Mission Hill building until a July 2017 digitization project. Digiscribe New England scanned all transcripts and Review Board comments at their Norwood, MA facility, July-November 2017. On February 13, 2018 the records were transferred from the Digiscribe facility to DCA's off-site storage at Iron Mountain, under the supervision of Liz Francis, University Records Manager. Custody of the records was transferred to DCA by JoAnn Jack, Registrar, ASE later that week.
    - Student folders, Abarca, Andrea - Acciardi, Patricia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.407 (Box 407)
      75 years
      General
      UA-2018-030
    - Student folders, Acevedo, Nicole - Adams, Sharon, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.239 (Box 239)
    - Student folders, Aibangbe, Prince - Agababian, Lucy, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.105 (Box 105)
    - Student folders, Albright, Elin - Aldridge, Leslie, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.207 (Box 207)
    - Student folders, Alexander, Shoshana - Allen, Riley, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.163 (Box 163)
    - Student folders, Allen, Judith - Elam, Amanda, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.383 (Box 383)
    - Student folders, Allen, Samantha - Alvarado, Daniel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.089 (Box 89)
    - Student folders, Anderson, Bryant - Andrieux, Lili, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.153 (Box 153)
    - Student folders, Andripoulos, Philipp - Aranda, Mario, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.228 (Box 228)
    - Student folders, Annese, Kelley - Alvarez, Angelique, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.292 (Box 292)
    - Student folders, Aranjo, Melanie Kidd - Arnholt, Chad, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.203 (Box 203)
    - Student folders, Arnias, Luis - Ashjian, Edward, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.097 (Box 97)
    - Student folders, Austin, John - Babii, Oksanna, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.334 (Box 334)
    - Student folders, Babin, Myriam - Baker, Kristen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.385 (Box 385)
    - Student folders, Baker, Marc - Barbot, Victoire, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.110 (Box 110)
    - Student folders, Barcelos, Christie - Summoner, Paul, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.093 (Box 93)
    - Student folders, Barrett, Andrea - Bartolo, Ana, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.211 (Box 211)
    - Student folders, Barton, Christine - Baxter, Joell, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.394 (Box 394)
    - Student folders, Bay, Elaine - Becco, Maria, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.398 (Box 398)
    - Student folders, Becher, Aviva - Beer, Linda, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.139 (Box 139)
    - Student folders, Beerits, Peter - Benjamin, Susan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.382 (Box 382)
    - Student folders, Benjamins, Erik - Berg, Paige, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.091 (Box 91)
      Also Mosca, Benjamin
    - Student folders, Berg, Sherry - Bernard, Willis, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.144 (Box 144)
    - Student folders, Bernardez, Maria - Bezdek, Joyce, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.114 (Box 114)
    - Student folders, Bhakdibhumi, Lerdpol - Binder, Michael, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.113 (Box 113)
    - Student folders, Bindewald, Alexandra - Blackman, Debra, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.343 (Box 343)
    - Student folders, Blackman, Emily - Block, Cynthia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.119 (Box 119)
    - Student folders, Block, Janet - Boettger, Kara, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.204 (Box 204)
    - Student folders, Boffi, Erica - Boogaerts, Yvonne, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.100 (Box 100)
    - Student folders, Boomer, Lisa - Bossi, Kathryn, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.123 (Box 123)
    - Student folders, Bossidy, Alice - Bowden, Sharon, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.111 (Box 111)
    - Student folders, Bowler, Daniel - Bragel, Christopher, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.164 (Box 164)
    - Student folders, Braginton-Smith, Dianna - Breeding, Julie, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.138 (Box 138)
    - Student folders, Brennecke, Michael - Brim, Latrice, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.295 (Box 295)
    - Student folders, Brill, Jane - Bronson Wells, Meredith, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.094 (Box 94)
    - Student folders, Bronstein, Meryl - Brown, Huns, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.330 (Box 330)
    - Student folders, Brown, Philana - Brumble, Nina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.090 (Box 90)
    - Student folders, Brun, Chandler - Buchanan, Alex, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.194 (Box 194)
    - Student folders, Budd, Stuart - Burkart, Heather, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.122 (Box 122)
    - Student folders, Burke, David - Buser, Reto, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.196 (Box 196)
    - Student folders, Bush, David - Caesar, Allison, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.187 (Box 187)
    - Student folders, Caesar, Jedediah - Camacho, Christiano, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.206 (Box 206)
    - Student folders, Camacho, Jess - Canzano, Charlotte, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.147 (Box 147)
    - Student folders, Cao, Guanlong - Carlson, Doris, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.109 (Box 109)
    - Student folders, Carlson, Elinor - Carroll, Christina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.120 (Box 120)
    - Student folders, Carroll, Dana - Carvalho, Lynne, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.348 (Box 348)
    - Student folders, Carvalho, Stacey - Caveney, Meghan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.154 (Box 154)
    - Student folders, Caveny, Charles - Chambers, Kathe, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.143 (Box 143)
    - Student folders, Chambers, Melanie - Chapuis, Katharina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.127 (Box 127)
    - Student folders, Charbonneau, Karen - Cheong, Melissa, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.118 (Box 118)
    - Student folders, Cheou, Annie - Chiotellis, Nicholas, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.117 (Box 117)
    - Student folders, Chipman, Danica - Chobanian, Jasmine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.150 (Box 150)
    - Student folders, Chong, Nicole - Chudler, Kelly, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.104 (Box 104)
    - Student folders, Chuensumran, Prim - Cintas, Nicholas, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.133 (Box 133)
    - Student folders, Cioffi, Gay - Clayton, Kevin, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.115 (Box 115)
    - Student folders, Cleanthes, Michael - Cochrane, Theresa, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.351 (Box 351)
    - Student folders, Cocke, John - Cohen, Sasha, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.126 (Box 126)
    - Student folders, Cohen, Stephanie - Collins, Jesse, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.121 (Box 121)
    - Student folders, Colindres, Alexandria - Condon, Leslie, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.116 (Box 116)
    - Student folders, Cone, Terry - Cook, Ruth, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.092 (Box 92)
    - Student folders, Cook, Sheryl - Corley, Jasmine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.158 (Box 158)
    - Student folders, Corman, Elizabeth - Counts, Angela, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.098 (Box 98)
    - Student folders, Courtnell, Ruth - Crawford, Kathleen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.197 (Box 197)
    - Student folders, Crawford, Paul - Cross, Melinda, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.146 (Box 146)
    - Student folders, Cross, Norman - Cummings, Tyrell, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.149 (Box 149)
    - Student folders, Cummins, Leslie - Dabiri, Shirine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.151 (Box 151)
    - Student folders, Dabney, Beatrice - Danaher, Ceara, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.128 (Box 128)
      Also Erickson, Sue Ellen
    - Student folders, Dancette-DeBresson, Connie - Davidson, Rhiannon "Bug", circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.208 (Box 208)
    - Student folders, Davidson, Deborah - Davis, Taylor (D. Taylor), circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.088 (Box 88)
    - Student folders, Davis, Tina - Decker, Charlene, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.148 (Box 148)
    - Student folders, De Martelly, Johanne - De Pietro, Jason, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.367 (Box 367)
    - Student folders, De Pippo, Richard - Deutz, Candice, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.135 (Box 135)
    - Student folders, Decker, Max - Delaney,Eve, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.160 (Box 160)
    - Student folders, Delaney, John - DeMarco, Kimberly, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.195 (Box 195)
      Also Alllen-Mills, Delaney
    - Student folders, Devaney, Elizabeth - Dichiara, Tatia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.152 (Box 152)
    - Student folders, Dickerson, Julie - Dire, Michael, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.188 (Box 188)
    - Student folders, Dirga, Carol - Dombeck, Christopher, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.107 (Box 107)
    - Student folders, Domingues, Grace - Doran, Thomas, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.125 (Box 125)
    - Student folders, Doran, Weldon - Drachman, Ann, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.108 (Box 108)
    - Student folders, Dragomer, Krista - DuBrino, Jared, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.214 (Box 214)
    - Student folders, Dudek, Katherine - Duncan, Nicholas, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.181 (Box 181)
    - Student folders, Duncan, Richard - Dusak, Jessica, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.124 (Box 124)
    - Student folders, Dusek, Alexander - Efstathiou, Eirene, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.314 (Box 314)
    - Student folders, Eberle, Alissa - Edwards, Philippa, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.301 (Box 301)
    - Student folders, Elkins, Tilke - Embree, Daniel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.141 (Box 141)
    - Student folders, Emers, Charles - Erdman, Jody, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.095 (Box 95)
    - Student folders, Erdman, Eric - Eustis, Sarag, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.101 (Box 101)
    - Student folders, Evans, Ann - Falconer, Tonia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.216 (Box 216)
    - Student folders, Falk, Perri - Farrington, Katherine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.220 (Box 220)
    - Student folders, Farsi, Raneem - Feasley, Joy, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.227 (Box 227)
      Also "Problem Files"
    - Student folders, Featherstone, Chuva - Fergus, Joseph, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.145 (Box 145)
    - Student folders, Ferguson, Caer - Fichtner, Timothy, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.217 (Box 217)
    - Student folders, Fidalgo, Jane - Fionte, Daniel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.223 (Box 223)
    - Student folders, Fiore, Andrea - Fitzgerald, Karen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.224 (Box 224)
    - Student folders, Fitzgerald, Keith - Floyd, Gerald, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.229 (Box 229)
    - Student folders, Floyd, Joseph - Forrester, Marlon, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.226 (Box 226)
    - Student folders, Forsberg, Eric - Fox, Lucy, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.210 (Box 210)
    - Student folders, Fox, Mary Ellen - Freedman, Daniel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.212 (Box 212)
    - Student folders, Freedman-Kaplow, Frances - Freysinger, Laura, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.209 (Box 209)
    - Student folders, Frias, Virginia - Fry, Kimberly, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.364 (Box 364)
      Also Faria, Kaitlyn
    - Student folders, Fryer, Philip - Funk, Carolyn, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.222 (Box 222)
    - Student folders, Funk, Celine - Gaines, Karen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.389 (Box 389)
    - Student folders, Gaines, Muriel - Garcia, Elizabeth, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.386 (Box 386)
    - Student folders, Garcia, Isha - Gary, Kathleen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.404 (Box 404)
    - Student folders, Gary, Ruth - Geisser, Peter, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.248 (Box 248)
    - Student folders, Gessner, Jennifer - Gilmore, William, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.419 (Box 419)
    - Student folders, Gessner, Lewis - Geissler, Elizabeth, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.331 (Box 331)
    - Student folders, Giese, Robert - Gisiger, Valerie, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.434 (Box 434)
    - Student folders, Goda, Akane - Goldman, Robert, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.402 (Box 402)
    - Student folders, Goldner, Jean - Gonzales, Teresa, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.237 (Box 237)
    - Student folders, Gooch, Virginia - Gorvett, Donald, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.392 (Box 392)
    - Student folders, Gorvett, Ralph - Graham, Thomas, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.232 (Box 232)
    - Student folders, Graham, Virginia - Gray, Tricia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.363 (Box 363)
    - Student folders, Grayson, Chelsea - Grey, Lori, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.372 (Box 372)
    - Student folders, Gricus, Brian - Gross, Lisa, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.378 (Box 378)
    - Student folders, Gross, Norman - Guillaume, Paul, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.247 (Box 247)
    - Student folders, Gugino, Gregory - Gutierrez, Marta, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.384 (Box 384)
    - Student folders, Gunta, Weston - Goblick, Brian, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.142 (Box 142)
    - Student folders, Gutshall, Danielle - Hagenbuch, Jennifer, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.175 (Box 175)
    - Student folders, Hager, Susan - Hall, Nikkia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.374 (Box 374)
    - Student folders, Hall, Jonathan - Hamrick, Alexander, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.353 (Box 353)
    - Student folders, Hamill, Mary - Hankins, Thomas, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.137 (Box 137)
    - Student folders, Hanley, Amanda - Harman, Forest, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.339 (Box 339)
    - Student folders, Harmandar, Cagil - Harrison, Hilary, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.336 (Box 336)
    - Student folders, Harrison, Laura - Hasan-Kahn, Alia, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.313 (Box 313)
    - Student folders, Haudenschild, Heidi - Hasin, Nina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.234 (Box 234)
    - Student folders, Hawkes, Dana - Heaton, Joel, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.352 (Box 352)
    - Student folders, Heaton, Kelly - Heltsley, Elizabeth, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.235 (Box 235)
    - Student folders, Helvey, William Kevin - Herr, Robin, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.225 (Box 225)
    - Student folders, Herrera, Jorge - Heynen, Chris, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.170 (Box 170)
    - Student folders, Heys, James - Hill, Jennifer, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.221 (Box 221)
    - Student folders, Hill, Kristina - Hirsig, Christina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.218 (Box 218)
    - Student folders, Hjortshoj, Justin - Hochschild, Stephen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.219 (Box 219)
    - Student folders, Hoe, Arthur - Hollander, Dean, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.176 (Box 176)
    - Student folders, Hollant, Richard - Honig, Jaclyn, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.420 (Box 420)
    - Student folders, Hopkins, Lindsay - Horwitz,Michael, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.249 (Box 249)
    - Student folders, Hoshino, Jun - Hoxie, Adriana, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.250 (Box 250)
    - Student folders, Hoyda, Lily - Hubley, Sara, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.309 (Box 309)
    - Student folders, Huckleberry, Jeff - Huh, Jo Eun, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.191 (Box 191)
    - Student folders, Huh, Won Jeon - Hurwitz, Dylan, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.238 (Box 238)
    - Student folders, Hundson, Ashley - Austin, David, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.106 (Box 106)
    - Student folders, Hurwitz, Laurie - Hydeman, Joshua, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.243 (Box 243)
    - Student folders, Hyer, Jane - Ippolito, Katherine, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.335 (Box 335)
    - Student folders, Ippolito, Salvatore - Ito, Atsuko, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.431 (Box 431)
    - Student folders, Ito, Rina - Jackson, Caleb, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.231 (Box 231)
    - Student folders, Jacks, Hilary - James, Ned, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.332 (Box 332)
    - Student folders, James, Ryan - Jefferson, Joshua, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.321 (Box 321)
    - Student folders, Jeffrey, Ian - Jigarjian, Mary, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.236 (Box 236)
    - Student folders, Jillson, Kenneth - Johnson, Ingrid, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.328 (Box 328)
    - Student folders, Johnson, Faith - Jonah, Kristen, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.251 (Box 251)
    - Student folders, Jonas, Joan (Edwards) - Jones, Traci, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.340 (Box 340)
    - Student folders, Jones, Tracy - Junker, Claude, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.246 (Box 246)
    - Student folders, Jurkowski, Allan - Kakeda, Tomoko, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.233 (Box 233)
    - Student folders, Kalaitzidou, Anthi - Kang, Minzee, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.186 (Box 186)
    - Student folders, Kang, Sun Yu - Karo, Andrea, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.245 (Box 245)
    - Student folders, Karpovich, Marisha - Kauders, Lee, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.322 (Box 322)
    - Student folders, Kaufman, Allison - Keefe, Thomas, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.179 (Box 179)
    - Student folders, Keegan, Nancy - Kelly, Susanne, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.140 (Box 140)
    - Student folders, Kenely, Matthew - Kelly, Schuyler, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.244 (Box 244)
    - Student folders, Kennedy, Lynda - Kikuchi, Naoko, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.240 (Box 240)
    - Student folders, Kilawee, Sean - Kim, Jeong Kyu, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.230 (Box 230)
    - Student folders, Kim, Jin - Sung - Kim, Soojin, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.241 (Box 241)
    - Student folders, Kim, Soo-Young - Kindem, Bjorn, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.411 (Box 411)
    - Student folders, Kinder, Elizabeth - Kirages, Chris, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.338 (Box 338)
    - Student folders, Kirby, Edward - Klemm, Maria, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.159 (Box 159)
    - Student folders, Klencheski, Kathryn - Kno, Julie, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.406 (Box 406)
    - Student folders, Knobel, Angela - Kothari, Neerja, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.252 (Box 252)
    - Student folders, Knott, Elizabeth - Konowitz, Hollie, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.415 (Box 415)
    - Student folders, Kotoch, Jason - Kriebel, Mrs. Richard, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.242 (Box 242)
    - Student folders, Krieble, Joshua - Kuhn, Ana, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.215 (Box 215)
    - Student folders, Kuhn, Christopher - Kwiatkowski, Cheryl, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.130 (Box 130)
    - Student folders, Kwei, Clarence - Lam, Ky, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.189 (Box 189)
    - Student folders, Lam, Owen - Lang, David, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.442 (Box 442)
    - Student folders, Lang, Elizabeth - Lapossy, Chrissy, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.272 (Box 272)
    - Student folders, Lappi, Laura - Latman, Dori, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.169 (Box 169)
    - Student folders, Lau, Nikki - Lazarakis, Christina, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.201 (Box 201)
    - Student folders, Lazare, Louise - Lee, April, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.253 (Box 253)
    - Student folders, Lee, Aaron - Lee, Jihoo, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.166 (Box 166)
    - Student folders, Lee, Jin Young - Lee, Timothy, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.423 (Box 423)
    - Student folders, Lee, Unsen - Lempert, Taliah, circa 1945 -- 2015; UA133.005.424 (Box 424)